I looked at what was happening around
me, and I saw a lot of podcasts focusing
on crypto. I saw a lot of media focusing
on crypto.
And I looked at
in my mind telescoping forward, what
would be the implications of me having
these four or five people on? There
would be
a definite short or intermediate term
reward. Lots of downloads, very happy
sponsors. So, what are the tradeoffs if
I commit doing four or five more
episodes on crypto? One is that I start
to filter out anyone in my audience
who's not
interested in crypto, most likely. That
is a very large sacrifice, number one.
Because I want a diverse audience.
Number two is that I would be training
myself
to succumb to audience capture.
And there's some great pieces that have
been written about audience capture. I
apologize that I can't remember the
author's name. It's really fantastic
piece.
But he starts with this example of a
YouTuber whose channel focused on him
gorging himself, eating these kind of
absurdly large meals. And he started off
pretty thin
and ended up, as he was rewarded for
these videos, as he felt he needed to
continue to rack up views serving people
what they wanted, he destroyed his
health completely. Became obese, put on
this mask, and if you wear a mask long
enough, you become the mask. I think
that's something that people miss.